You don't understand.
For us, kissing is as
important as any part.
Yeah, right!
You serious?
Oh, yeah.
- Everything is in that first kiss.
- Absolutely.
For us, kissing's an opening act..
like the comedian
you have to sit through..
before Pink Floyd comes out.
And it's not that
we don't like the comedian.
It's just that that's not
why we bought the ticket.
The problem is, no matter
how great the show was..
you girls are looking
for the comedian again.
We're in the car, fighting traffic,
just trying to stay awake.
Word of advice:
Bring back the comedian.
Or next time you'll find yourself
listening to that album alone.
Are we still talking about sex?
The One With the Sonogram at the End
No, it's good. It is good.
It's just that Doesn't she seem
a little angry?
Well, she has issues.
Does she?
Try to live with "Mr. I'm Evolving."