This is unbelievable.
It's been half an hour.
If this was a cartoon, you'd be
looking like a ham right about now.
There's the waitress.
Excuse me, miss.
JOEY: Hello, miss?
- It's Phoebe.
CHANDLER: Hi.
- Hi.
Okay, will that be all?
Wait, wait.
What are you doing here?
Yeah, um, I was over there...
...then you said, "Excuse me, miss."
So now I'm here.
No, no. How come you're working here?
Right. Because it's close to where I live,
and the aprons are really cute.
Can we start over?
- Yeah. Okay, great. I'll be over here.
- No, no, no, no.
I don't know whether he's testing me
or just acting out...
...but my monkey is out of control.
He keeps erasing
the messages on my machine.
Supposedly by accident.
Oh, yeah, I've done that.
And three days in a row, he got
to the newspaper before I did...
...and peed all over the crossword.
I've never done that.
Now tell me she doesn't look
exactly like her sister.
I'm saying I see a difference.
They're twins.
I don't care.
Phoebe's Phoebe. Ursula's hot.
You know that thing
when we talk about things?
- Let's not do that anymore.
- Okay.
ROSS: Hey, guys.
ALL: Hey.
Hey, Pheebs.
Guess who we saw today.
Ooh. Oh, fun. Okay.
- Um, Liam Neeson.
- No.
- Morley Safer.
JOEY: Nope.
- The woman who cuts my hair.
JOEY: No.
Look, this could be a really long game.
Your sister, Ursula.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
She works at that place, uh...
Riff's. Yeah, I know.
Oh, you do? She said you guys
haven't talked in years.
Hmm? Yeah.
So, um, is she fat?
Not from where I was standing.
Where were you standing?
Uh, Pheebs, so you guys
just don't get along?
It's mostly just dumb
sister stuff, you know?
Everyone always thought of her
as the pretty one.
Oh. Oh. She was the first to walk...
...even though I did it
later that same day.
To my parents, by then it was,
"Yeah, what else is new?"
ROSS:
Oh.
Pheebs, I'm sorry. I've gotta go.
I've got Lamaze class.
Oh, and I've got earth science,
but I'll catch you in gym?
So is this just gonna be you and Carol?
No. Susan will be there too.
We've got dads. We've got lesbians.
The whole parenting team.
Well, isn't that gonna be weird?
No. It might have been at first...
...but now I'm comfortable
with the situation.
- Ross, that's my jacket.
- I know.
Hi. We're the Rostens.
I'm J.C. And he's Michael.
And we're having a boy and a girl.
Good for you.
Alrighty, next?
Hi. Um, I'm, uh... Ahem.
I'm Ross Geller.
And, uh, that's my boy in there.
And, uh, this is Carol Willick,
and this is Susan Bunch.
Susan is, um, Carol's...
[MUMBLES]
Who's next?
I'm sorry, Susan is?
- Susan is Carol's friend.
- Life partner.
Like buddies.
Like lovers.
You know how close women can get.
- Susan and I live together.
- I was married to her.
- Carol. Not me.
- It's a little complicated.
- But we're fine.
- Absolutely.
So, twins. Ha.
That's like two births.
Ouch.
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
[MIMICS INTERCOM BUZZING]
- To you too, Helen.
HELEN [OVER INTERCOM]:
Nina Bookbinder is here to see you.
Oh. Okay, send her in.
Hi.
- Hi, Nina. Come on in.
- You wanted to see me?
Uh, yes.
Uh, I was just going over your data.
You've been postdating
your Friday numbers.
Which is bad, because?
- Well, it throws my WENUS out of whack.
- Ha, ha.
Excuse me?
WENUS. Ahem.
- Weekly Estimated...
- Oh, Net Usage Statistics.
Right. Gotcha, gotcha.
Won't happen again. I wouldn't
want to do anything to hurt your...
...WENUS.
It's not just that she's cute, okay?
It's just that...
...she's really, really cute.
It doesn't matter. You don't dip
your pen in the company ink.